

Prithviraj Kadiyala

Graduate Research Assistant



Summary

Graduate Research Assistant with 2+ years of experience Leading Team in Designing and developing website using various algorithms to solve the problem of Data Management for US Department of Agriculture while understanding key features of Business approach towards commercializing product. Team lead for designing and developing the remote configuration of Network Management Systems using Cisco Packet Tracer simulation tool. Looking to utilize Developer, Time management and Team Leading skill in the position of Software Development Engineer/Full-Stack Developer.



Experience

2016-08 - present

Graduate Research Assistant (OU)

Responsibilities:

- Design and develop Website for Database Management at US Department of Agriculture.
- Proposing and developing solutions based on the interactions with Animal Scientists and Veterinarians.
- Experience the Business aspect of conducting research.
- Lead a team of 5 to complete a project.
- Product Testing before launch.

2015-06 -2016-05

Team Lead (BVBCET)

Responsibilities:

- Study different RFCs(Request for Communications) available for different routing systems.
- Study the OIDs(Object Identifiers) required for NMS.
- Configuring routing devices and routing protocols.
- Build a Network Management System.

প্র

Education

2016-08 -

University of Oklahoma(OU)

- 2018-12
- M.S in Electrical and Computer Engineering.
- President of ECE- Graduate Student Committee.
- Speaker at Databite Workshop OUDALAB

Courses: Database Management Systems, Algorithm Analysis, Applied statistical methods, Computer Hardware Design, Image Processing

2012-08 -2016-05

B.V.Bhoomaraddi College of Engineering and Technology (BVBCET)

- Bachelors in Electronics and Communication Engineering
- General Secretary for ECE in 2016.
- Junior Head for National Level Tech Fest 2015.
- Organized 20+ events and 6 workshops.

Courses: C, Data Structures, Object-Oriented Programming, Automotive Electronics, Accounting and Financial Management



Address

936 Deonne Circle, Norman, OK-73071

Phone

+1 (405)227-6525

E-mail

prithvirajkadiyala@ou.edu

Personal Website

https://prithvirajkadiyala.github.io

LinkedIn

https://linkedin.com/in/prithvirajkadiyala-003073a3/



Python, mySQL, GitHub, AJAX, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Flask



Matlab, Git, R, Linux, C, VHDL



Algorithm Analysis, Hardware Design



Leadership, Communication

